[法語]
少年泰坦
猶大契約
m 200 -1 l 200 13 l 19 13 b 14 12 14 6 14 6 b 14 6 14 0 19 -1
m 38 -1 l 44 6 l 38 13 l 19 13 b 14 12 14 6 14 6 b 14 6 14 0 19 -1
翻譯     寓
翻譯     小願8
翻譯     tifhadu
校對     隔壁家的孩子
時間軸    小願8
壓制     寓
m 211 -8 b 217 -6 217 -4 217 -2 l 217 24 b 217 26 217 29 211 31 l 31 31 b 26 29 26 26 26 24 l 26 -2 b 26 -4 26 -6 31 -8
m 38 11 b 41 11 45 11 49 11 b 48 15 48 19 48 22 b 45 22 41 22 38 22 b 38 19 38 15 38 11 m 118 93 b 121 93 125 93 128 93 b 128 96 128 99 128 104 b 125 104 121 104 117 104 b 118 99 118 96 118 93 m 129 23 b 125 23 122 23 118 23 b 118 19 118 16 118 13 b 122 13 125 13 129 13 b 129 16 129 20 129 23 m 51 88 b 51 87 51 86 51 85 b 53 85 54 85 55 85 b 55 86 55 87 55 88 b 54 88 53 88 51 88 m 66 103 b 66 101 66 100 66 99 b 67 99 68 99 69 99 b 69 100 69 102 69 103 b 68 103 67 103 66 103 m 62 95 b 64 95 65 95 66 95 b 66 97 66 98 66 99 b 65 99 64 99 62 99 b 62 98 62 97 62 95 m 111 45 b 111 44 111 42 111 41 b 111 41 112 41 114 41 b 114 42 114 44 114 45 b 112 45 112 45 111 45 m 96 74 b 96 73 96 71 96 70 b 96 70 98 70 99 70 b 99 71 99 73 99 74 b 98 74 97 74 96 74 m 88 99 b 87 99 85 99 84 99 b 84 101 84 102 84 103 b 83 103 82 103 81 103 b 81 102 81 101 81 99 b 80 99 79 99 77 99 b 77 98 77 97 77 95 b 76 95 74 95 73 95 b 73 94 73 93 73 92 b 76 92 79 92 81 92 b 81 93 81 94 81 95 b 83 95 85 95 88 95 b 88 97 88 98 88 99 m 85 56 b 84 56 83 56 81 56 b 81 55 81 53 81 52 b 83 52 83 52 85 52 b 85 53 85 55 85 56 m 114 67 b 113 67 112 67 110 67 b 110 68 110 70 110 71 b 108 71 106 71 103 70 b 103 69 103 68 103 67 b 104 67 105 67 106 67 b 106 66 106 64 106 63 b 105 63 104 63 103 63 b 103 65 103 66 103 67 b 100 67 98 67 96 67 b 96 68 96 69 96 70 b 95 70 93 70 92 70 b 92 69 92 68 92 67 b 91 67 89 67 88 67 b 88 66 88 64 88 63 b 92 63 95 63 99 63 b 99 62 99 61 99 59 b 98 59 97 59 96 59 b 96 57 96 55 96 52 b 95 52 93 52 92 52 b 92 51 92 50 92 48 b 93 48 94 48 96 48 b 96 47 96 46 96 45 b 99 45 101 45 103 45 b 103 46 103 48 103 49 b 102 49 101 49 100 49 b 100 51 100 53 100 56 b 101 56 102 56 103 56 b 103 53 103 51 103 49 b 104 49 106 49 107 49 b 107 48 107 46 107 45 b 108 45 110 45 111 45 b 111 47 111 48 111 49 b 112 49 112 49 114 49 b 114 50 114 51 114 52 b 113 52 112 52 111 52 b 111 53 111 55 111 56 b 113 56 115 56 118 56 b 118 59 118 61 118 63 b 117 63 115 63 114 63 b 114 62 114 61 114 60 b 112 60 112 60 111 60 b 111 61 111 62 111 63 b 112 63 113 63 114 63 b 114 64 114 66 114 67 m 33 106 b 33 107 33 108 33 110 b 32 110 31 110 29 110 b 30 108 30 107 30 106 b 31 106 31 106 33 106 m 33 99 b 33 100 33 101 33 102 b 32 102 31 102 30 102 b 30 101 30 100 30 99 b 31 99 32 99 33 99 m 37 95 b 36 97 36 98 36 99 b 35 99 34 99 33 99 l 33 99 b 33 98 33 96 33 95 l 33 95 b 34 95 35 95 37 95 m 37 80 b 37 79 37 79 37 77 b 38 77 39 77 41 77 b 41 78 41 79 41 80 l 41 80 b 39 80 38 80 37 80 m 38 37 b 38 36 38 35 38 33 b 39 33 39 33 41 33 b 41 34 41 36 41 37 b 39 37 39 37 38 37 b 38 37 38 37 38 37 m 45 74 b 43 74 42 74 41 74 b 41 72 41 71 41 70 b 41 70 41 70 41 70 b 42 70 43 70 45 70 l 45 70 b 45 71 45 72 45 74 m 41 48 b 41 47 41 46 41 44 b 42 44 43 44 45 44 b 44 45 44 47 44 48 b 43 48 42 48 41 48 b 41 48 41 48 41 48 m 49 37 b 49 38 49 40 49 41 b 47 41 46 41 45 41 b 45 40 45 38 45 37 b 46 37 47 37 49 37 b 49 37 49 37 49 37 m 52 55 b 51 55 50 55 48 55 b 48 54 48 53 48 52 b 50 52 51 52 52 52 l 52 52 b 52 53 52 54 52 55 m 89 5 b 91 5 92 5 92 5 b 92 6 92 7 92 9 b 92 9 90 9 89 9 b 89 7 89 6 89 5 m 33 95 b 32 95 31 95 30 95 b 30 93 30 90 30 88 b 31 88 32 88 33 88 l 33 88 b 33 90 33 93 33 95 m 37 63 b 35 63 32 63 30 62 b 30 61 30 60 30 59 b 32 59 35 59 37 59 b 37 59 37 59 37 59 b 37 60 37 61 37 63 b 37 63 37 63 37 63 m 38 37 b 38 38 38 40 38 41 b 35 41 32 41 30 41 b 30 40 30 38 30 37 b 32 37 35 37 38 37 m 96 12 b 96 10 96 8 96 5 b 98 5 99 5 100 5 b 100 7 100 10 100 12 l 100 12 b 99 12 98 12 96 12 m 93 19 b 93 17 93 15 93 12 b 94 12 95 12 96 12 l 96 12 b 96 15 96 17 96 19 l 96 19 b 95 19 94 19 93 19 m 110 78 b 112 78 115 78 117 78 b 117 79 117 80 117 82 b 115 82 112 82 110 82 b 110 80 110 79 110 78 b 110 78 110 78 110 78 m 133 60 b 133 60 134 60 136 60 b 136 62 136 65 136 67 b 134 67 134 67 133 67 l 133 67 b 133 65 133 62 133 60 m 33 88 b 33 87 33 86 33 84 b 32 84 31 84 30 84 b 30 83 30 82 30 80 b 32 80 35 80 37 80 l 37 80 b 37 83 37 86 37 88 l 37 88 b 36 88 34 88 33 88 m 43 106 b 42 106 42 106 41 106 b 41 108 41 109 41 110 b 39 110 38 110 36 110 b 36 107 36 105 36 102 b 39 102 41 102 43 102 b 43 104 43 105 43 106 m 55 106 b 55 108 55 109 55 110 b 53 110 50 110 47 110 b 47 108 47 105 47 102 b 49 102 50 102 51 102 l 51 102 b 51 104 51 105 51 106 b 53 106 54 106 55 106 m 60 37 b 55 37 52 37 49 37 l 49 37 b 49 36 49 34 49 33 b 52 33 55 33 60 34 b 60 35 60 36 60 37 b 60 37 60 37 60 37 m 100 12 b 102 12 104 13 107 13 b 107 14 107 15 107 16 b 106 16 105 16 104 16 b 104 17 104 18 104 19 b 102 19 101 19 100 19 l 100 19 b 100 17 100 15 100 12 m 37 48 b 36 48 35 48 34 48 b 34 51 34 53 34 55 b 32 55 31 55 30 55 b 30 52 30 48 30 44 b 32 44 35 44 37 44 b 37 45 37 47 37 48 m 37 59 b 37 55 37 52 37 48 l 37 48 b 39 48 40 48 41 48 l 41 48 b 41 51 41 53 41 55 b 42 55 43 55 44 55 b 44 56 44 57 44 59 b 42 59 39 59 37 59 b 37 59 37 59 37 59 m 121 71 b 121 72 121 73 121 74 b 118 74 114 74 110 74 l 110 74 b 110 73 110 72 110 71 b 112 71 113 71 114 71 b 114 70 114 68 114 67 b 115 67 116 67 118 67 b 118 68 118 70 118 71 b 119 71 120 71 121 71 m 37 63 b 38 63 39 63 41 63 b 41 65 41 67 41 70 b 41 70 41 70 41 70 b 39 70 38 70 37 70 b 37 71 37 72 37 74 b 35 73 32 73 30 73 b 30 72 30 71 30 70 b 31 70 32 70 34 70 b 34 68 34 67 34 66 b 35 66 35 66 37 66 b 37 65 37 64 37 63 m 70 37 b 73 37 75 37 78 37 l 78 37 b 78 38 78 40 78 41 b 76 41 75 41 74 41 b 74 42 74 44 74 45 b 75 45 76 45 77 45 b 77 46 77 47 77 48 b 75 48 72 48 70 48 l 70 48 b 70 45 70 41 70 37 m 111 38 b 111 37 111 36 111 34 b 118 34 125 34 133 34 b 133 36 133 37 133 38 l 133 38 b 125 38 118 38 111 38 m 129 49 b 129 50 129 51 129 52 b 130 52 131 52 133 52 b 133 55 133 57 133 60 l 133 60 b 129 60 125 60 122 60 b 122 59 122 57 122 56 b 123 56 124 56 125 56 b 125 53 125 51 125 49 l 125 49 b 126 49 128 49 129 49 m 133 38 b 134 38 135 38 136 38 b 136 41 136 43 136 45 b 135 45 134 45 133 45 b 133 47 133 48 133 49 b 131 49 130 49 129 49 l 129 49 b 129 48 129 47 129 45 b 127 45 126 45 125 45 b 125 47 125 48 125 49 l 125 49 b 123 49 121 49 118 49 b 118 48 118 47 118 45 b 119 45 121 45 121 45 b 122 44 122 42 122 41 b 125 41 129 41 133 42 b 133 40 133 39 133 38 m 133 74 b 133 74 134 74 136 74 b 136 77 136 79 136 82 b 132 82 129 82 125 82 b 125 78 125 74 125 71 b 124 71 123 71 121 71 l 121 71 b 122 68 122 66 122 63 b 124 63 126 63 129 63 b 129 64 129 66 129 67 b 130 67 131 67 133 67 l 133 67 b 133 70 133 72 133 74 b 131 74 130 74 129 74 b 129 75 129 76 129 78 b 130 78 131 78 132 78 b 132 77 133 75 133 74 m 103 85 b 103 86 103 87 103 89 b 104 89 105 89 106 89 b 106 95 106 101 106 107 b 105 107 104 107 103 107 b 103 108 103 109 103 110 b 100 110 98 110 95 110 b 95 109 95 108 95 106 b 96 106 98 106 99 106 b 99 105 99 104 99 103 b 98 103 96 103 95 103 b 95 102 95 101 95 99 b 94 99 93 99 92 99 l 92 99 b 92 98 92 97 92 95 b 94 95 97 96 99 96 b 99 97 99 98 99 99 b 100 99 102 99 102 99 b 102 97 102 95 103 92 b 101 92 100 92 99 92 b 99 90 99 87 99 85 b 100 85 102 85 103 85 m 92 99 b 92 102 92 104 92 106 b 91 106 89 106 88 106 b 88 108 88 109 88 110 b 78 110 68 110 58 110 b 58 109 58 108 59 106 b 57 106 56 106 55 106 l 55 106 b 55 105 55 104 55 102 l 55 102 b 59 102 62 103 66 103 b 66 104 66 105 66 106 b 69 106 71 106 73 106 b 73 105 73 104 73 103 b 74 103 76 103 77 103 b 77 104 77 105 77 106 b 80 106 82 106 84 106 b 84 105 84 104 84 103 b 85 103 87 103 88 103 b 88 102 88 101 88 99 b 89 99 91 99 92 99 m 52 26 b 52 20 52 14 52 8 b 46 8 40 8 34 8 b 34 14 34 20 34 26 b 40 26 46 26 52 26 m 30 30 b 30 21 30 13 31 5 b 39 5 47 5 55 5 b 55 13 55 21 55 30 b 47 30 39 30 30 30 m 114 107 b 120 107 126 107 131 107 b 131 101 131 95 132 89 b 126 89 120 89 114 89 b 114 95 114 101 114 107 m 110 110 b 110 102 110 94 110 85 b 119 85 127 85 136 85 b 136 94 136 102 136 111 b 127 110 118 110 110 110 m 133 9 b 126 9 121 9 115 9 b 115 15 115 21 115 27 b 121 27 127 27 133 27 b 133 21 133 15 133 9 m 111 30 b 111 22 111 14 111 5 b 119 5 128 5 137 6 b 136 14 136 22 136 31 b 128 31 119 30 111 30 m 74 23 b 73 23 72 23 70 23 b 70 25 70 28 70 30 b 69 30 68 30 67 30 b 67 26 67 23 67 19 b 68 19 69 19 70 19 b 70 18 70 17 70 15 b 69 15 68 15 67 15 b 67 17 67 18 67 19 b 66 19 65 19 64 19 b 63 23 63 26 63 30 b 62 30 61 30 60 30 b 60 22 60 13 60 5 b 61 5 62 5 64 5 b 64 7 64 10 64 12 b 65 12 65 12 66 12 b 66 10 66 7 66 5 b 68 5 69 5 71 5 b 71 6 71 7 70 9 b 73 9 75 9 78 9 b 78 7 78 6 78 5 b 79 5 81 5 82 5 b 82 6 82 7 82 9 b 83 9 84 9 85 9 b 85 10 85 11 85 12 b 87 12 87 12 89 12 b 89 13 89 14 88 16 b 85 15 81 15 78 15 b 78 14 78 13 78 12 b 76 12 76 12 74 12 b 74 13 74 14 74 15 b 76 15 77 15 78 15 b 78 17 78 18 78 19 b 77 19 76 19 74 19 b 74 21 74 22 74 23 m 48 91 b 51 91 55 91 58 91 b 58 88 58 85 58 81 b 55 80 51 80 48 80 b 48 85 48 88 48 91 m 41 80 b 42 80 43 80 45 80 b 45 78 45 76 45 74 l 45 74 b 46 74 47 74 48 74 l 48 74 b 48 75 48 76 48 77 b 51 77 55 77 59 77 b 59 75 59 72 59 70 b 60 70 61 70 63 70 l 63 70 b 63 74 62 77 62 81 b 64 81 65 81 66 81 b 66 83 66 86 66 88 b 69 88 71 88 73 88 l 73 88 b 73 90 73 91 73 92 b 72 92 71 92 70 92 b 70 93 70 94 70 95 b 68 95 67 95 66 95 b 66 94 66 93 66 92 b 65 92 64 92 62 92 b 62 93 62 94 62 95 b 61 95 60 95 59 95 b 59 97 59 98 59 99 b 57 99 56 99 55 99 b 55 101 55 101 55 102 l 55 102 b 54 102 53 102 51 102 l 51 102 b 51 101 51 100 51 99 b 50 99 49 99 48 99 b 48 98 48 97 48 95 b 46 95 45 95 44 95 b 44 97 44 98 44 99 b 43 99 42 99 41 99 b 41 98 41 97 41 95 b 39 95 38 95 37 95 l 37 95 b 37 93 37 90 37 88 l 37 88 b 39 88 41 88 44 88 b 44 87 44 86 44 85 b 43 85 42 85 41 85 b 41 83 41 82 41 80 m 85 26 b 85 28 85 29 85 30 b 87 30 88 30 88 30 b 88 29 88 28 88 26 b 88 26 87 26 85 26 m 85 41 b 86 41 88 41 88 41 b 88 38 88 36 88 34 b 87 34 87 34 85 34 b 85 36 85 38 85 41 m 100 19 b 100 23 100 27 100 30 b 101 30 102 30 103 30 b 103 28 103 26 104 23 b 105 23 106 23 107 23 b 107 28 107 33 107 38 b 108 38 110 38 111 38 l 111 38 b 111 39 111 40 111 41 b 110 41 108 41 107 41 b 107 42 107 44 107 45 b 106 45 104 45 103 45 b 103 44 103 42 103 41 b 102 41 101 41 100 41 b 100 40 100 39 100 38 b 101 38 102 38 103 38 b 103 37 103 35 103 34 b 102 34 101 34 100 34 b 100 36 100 37 100 38 b 98 38 95 38 92 37 b 92 40 92 42 92 45 b 89 45 88 45 85 45 b 85 46 85 47 85 48 b 83 48 83 48 81 48 b 81 45 81 41 81 37 b 80 37 79 37 78 37 l 78 37 b 78 36 78 36 78 34 b 77 34 76 34 74 34 b 74 30 74 26 74 23 l 74 23 b 75 23 76 23 78 23 b 78 25 78 28 78 30 b 79 30 80 30 81 30 b 81 28 81 25 81 23 b 83 23 84 23 85 23 b 85 22 85 21 85 19 b 88 19 90 19 93 19 l 93 19 b 92 23 92 27 92 30 b 93 30 95 30 96 30 b 96 27 96 23 96 19 l 96 19 b 98 19 99 19 100 19 m 85 81 b 85 82 85 83 85 85 b 86 85 87 85 88 85 b 88 83 88 82 88 81 b 87 81 86 81 85 81 m 110 78 b 109 78 108 78 107 78 b 107 80 107 83 107 85 b 105 85 104 85 103 85 l 103 85 b 103 84 103 83 103 81 b 100 81 98 81 95 81 b 95 83 95 86 95 89 b 94 89 93 89 92 89 b 92 90 92 91 92 92 b 90 92 89 92 88 92 b 88 91 88 90 88 89 b 87 89 86 89 84 89 b 84 90 84 91 84 92 b 83 92 81 92 81 92 b 81 91 81 90 81 89 b 78 89 76 89 73 88 l 73 88 b 73 86 73 83 73 81 b 75 81 76 81 77 81 b 77 82 77 83 77 85 b 79 85 80 85 80 85 b 80 83 80 82 81 81 b 79 81 78 81 77 81 b 77 76 77 71 77 67 b 79 67 80 67 81 67 b 81 66 81 64 81 63 b 80 63 79 63 77 63 b 77 64 77 66 77 67 b 76 67 75 67 74 67 l 74 67 b 74 64 74 61 74 59 l 74 59 b 77 59 81 59 85 59 b 85 58 85 57 85 56 l 85 56 b 87 56 89 56 92 56 b 92 57 92 58 92 59 b 91 59 89 59 88 59 b 88 61 88 61 88 63 b 87 63 86 63 85 63 b 85 66 85 68 85 70 b 86 70 87 70 88 70 b 88 72 88 75 88 78 b 89 78 91 78 92 78 b 92 76 92 75 92 74 b 93 74 95 74 96 74 b 96 75 96 76 96 78 b 98 78 100 78 103 78 b 103 76 103 75 103 74 b 106 74 108 74 110 74 l 110 74 b 110 75 110 76 110 78 m 45 70 b 45 67 45 66 45 63 b 47 63 49 63 52 63 b 52 60 52 57 52 55 l 52 55 b 53 55 54 55 55 55 b 55 54 55 53 55 52 b 57 52 58 52 59 52 b 59 51 59 49 59 48 b 58 48 57 48 55 48 b 55 49 55 51 55 52 b 54 52 53 52 52 52 l 52 52 b 52 51 52 49 52 48 b 51 48 50 48 49 48 b 49 47 49 45 49 44 b 50 44 50 44 51 44 b 51 43 51 42 51 41 b 54 41 57 41 60 41 b 60 40 60 38 60 37 l 60 37 b 60 37 61 37 63 37 b 63 36 63 35 63 34 b 66 34 68 34 70 34 b 70 35 70 36 70 37 l 70 37 b 69 37 68 37 66 37 b 66 38 66 40 66 41 b 65 41 64 41 63 41 b 63 43 63 46 63 48 b 65 48 68 48 70 48 l 70 48 b 70 49 70 51 70 52 b 72 52 73 52 74 52 b 74 55 74 57 74 59 l 74 59 b 73 59 72 59 70 59 b 70 61 70 64 70 67 b 72 67 73 67 74 67 l 74 67 b 74 69 74 71 74 74 b 72 74 71 74 70 74 b 70 75 70 76 70 77 b 69 77 68 77 66 77 b 66 75 66 72 66 70 b 65 70 64 70 63 70 l 63 70 b 63 68 63 65 62 63 b 64 63 65 63 66 63 b 66 61 66 60 66 59 b 65 59 64 59 63 59 b 63 58 63 57 63 55 b 61 55 61 55 59 55 b 59 57 59 58 59 59 b 61 59 62 59 63 59 b 63 60 63 61 63 63 b 60 63 58 63 55 63 b 55 64 55 65 55 66 b 54 66 53 66 52 66 b 52 67 51 68 51 70 b 53 70 54 70 55 70 b 55 71 55 72 55 74 b 53 74 50 74 48 74 l 48 74 b 48 72 48 71 48 70 b 46 70 45 70 45 70
掃瞄二維碼
小願8壓制組
或QQ搜索
小願8壓制組原創翻譯
現在
週年紀念日 快樂
泰拉
處理完成
五年前
你就不能開快點嗎
Speed it up, will you?
你開車跟老太婆一樣
You drive like my granny.
在一堆車子中 我有什麼辦法
We're moving with the flow of traffic.
什麼時候輪我開
When do I get to drive?
我的車 所以 不
My car, so, never.
我在創建一個推特賬戶
Ooh, I'm gonna sign in this thing called Twitter.
就像你可以吧我喜歡吃披薩發出去
You put up what you're thinking like, I love pizza,
或者 我正在吃披薩  甚至是 披薩太棒了
or I'm having pizza now, or even pizza is awesome.
你們每天腦子裏不會只有披薩吧
All your thoughts don't have to be pizza related.
誰說的
Says who?
嘿 我們可以在這時
Hey, I could order a pizza,
定一個披薩
while we're puttering along here.
噢 好主意
Ooh, great idea.
馬上就能吃上披薩咯
Gonna have pizza soon.
已推送
First twit sent.
那是什麼玩意
What the heck is that?
閃電俠 去看下 收到
- Flash, go find out. - On it.
報告 你需要自己來看
- Report. - You need to see for yourself.
我沒法完全確定
I'm not totally sure.
終於有事做了 我們先阻止那恐怖五人組
Big week for us. First, we stop the fearsome five.
他們一定會這麼說
They were so pissed.
你們要為此付出付出代價
You'll pay for interfering with us.
什麼什麼的
Blah, blah, blah.
先做正事
And now we get to stop an alien brawl.
我們該站哪一邊
Which side do we join?
不是吧 不能以貌取人
- Really? - Looks can be deceiving.
少年泰坦 出擊
Titans, go!
這個決定可與她很性感沒一點關係
And the fact that she's hot has nothing to do with it.
閃開 蜥蜴唇
Buzz off, lizard lips!
借過 抱歉
Coming through. Excuse me.
抱歉
Excusez-moi
我想長髮公主想告訴我們些什麼
I think Rapunzel is trying to tell us something.
快手 你有足夠大的傢伙能把那玩意關上嗎
Speedy, you got something loud to close that thing?
沒問題 老大
Got you covered, boss.
這我可沒料到
I did not see that coming.
謝謝你
Thank you.
我是來自塔馬蘭的柯莉安妲
I am Koriand'r of Tamaran.
我們一族人可以通過親吻習得對方的語言
Our kind can learn language from the act of kissing.
不錯
Useful.
你還好嗎
Are you all right?
我的姐妹 柯曼得 篡權了王位
My sister, Komand'r, staged a coup and took the throne.
我不得不逃走
I had to flee.
但我很快就會回去
But I will soon return.
好吧 你可以跟我們呆在一起 直到你想出解決辦法來
Well, you can stay with us until you figure it out.
好嗎
Okay?
好的 請麻煩你
Yes, please.
我尋求兩到三天的庇護
I will ask sanctuary for two or three days.
最長一周
A week at the longest.
讓我來為你介紹我的朋友們
Let me introduce you to my friends.
哦對了 我能說點西班牙語
Oh, by the way, I speak some Spanish,
倘若你想學的話...
if you wanna learn that.
還有法語
Second year high school French.
歡迎來到少年泰坦
Welcome to the Teen Titans.
小心點你個蠢貨
Careful, you fool.
這設備比你的命都值錢
This equipment is worth more than your lives.
什麼
What?
少年泰坦在不到一分鐘的時間裏就會找過來
The Titans will be there in less than a minute.
我怎麼沒看出來
I see no signs of that.
信 或者不信 你的選擇
Believe, don't believe, your choice.
他們有防備
They're ready.
可惜太慢了
They're slow.
我還沒有回貼
I hardly had time to answer a post.
爬上去太明顯了 而且還有月光
It's a tough climb, especially in this moonlight.
夜翼
Nightwing.
它們會發現我們的
They're bound to spot us.
夜翼
Nightwing.
如果我們等那些雲
If we wait for those clouds...
迪克
Dick!
幹嘛
What?
土石女會把我們帶上去的
Terra is taking us up there.
是嗎
She is?
是 這兒所有髒活都是我的
Yeah, I do all the dirty work around here.
往上
Going up.
你離開太久了 牛仔
You've been gone a long time, cowboy.
行動
Let's move.
安靜
Quiet down.
聖甲蟲在害怕
The bug is nervous.
我也沒多少信心
I'm not feeling too good about this myself.
你怎麼能這麼冷靜
How come you're so calm?
因為你從沒當過地鼠
You have never been a gopher.
聖甲蟲 停下來
Scarab, stop.
你最好控制住那東西 甲殼蟲
Control that thing, Beetle,
要麼我就替你動手了
or I'll control it for you.
你打算在這地方舞刀弄槍
You're going to have a sword fight in here?
要不給你換個更像樣點的地方  比如掃帚間
How about some place roomier like a broom closet?
所有人 冷靜下來
Everyone, calm down.
敵人就在我們上面
The enemy is above us.
任務是一切
You have to channel all your thoughts to that.
記住 這些不是一般的敵人
Remember, these opponents are different.
呃 就像柯莉告訴你們的那樣
Uh, as Kori will tell you.
不不 沒關係請繼續講
No, keep going.
自從我離開泰坦 我一直在研究這些敵人
I've been studying them since I left the Titans.
他們是極端狂熱份子
They're zealots, extremists.
為了打倒你 他們可以不眨眼睛就犧牲掉自己
They'll sacrifice themselves without hesitation to get to you.
所以 我們得盡快打敗他們 越快越好
So, the quicker we take them down, the better.
這樣差不多了
That about cover it?
講的非常好
Very well said.
土石女 你還能堅持住嗎
Terra, can you do this?
當然 倘若你們都閉嘴的話
Yes, if you'd all shut up.
現在距離地板只有六英尺
We're six inches under the floor.
誰想敲敲門
Who wants to knock?
泰坦 出擊
Titans, go!
謝謝帶我們潛入了這個壓根沒法潛入的蜂巢基地 土石女
Thanks for getting us into the impenetrable H.I.V.E base, Terra.
是啊 你是最棒的
Yeah, you're the best.
這個壞蛋是你的 老媽
This bad guy is yours, mama.
土石女 跟緊我們
Terra, stay with us.
說得好像我一沒你們就不行了
Like I couldn't take out all these jokers by myself.
我們這裏已經暴露了
We've been compromised.
遺棄基地
Abandon the base.
他們準備得還不錯
They prepared well.
反應也迅速
Their reaction time is much better.
羅賓 別再恭維這些壞蛋了
Robin, stop complementing the bad guys.
至少有一點他說對了 時刻準備著
But he's right. Be ready for anything.
這些傢伙的裝備肯定是批發的
These dudes must buy their bad guy stuff in bulk.
要不我們試試你上週末教我的那個怎麼樣
How about we do that move you taught me last weekend?
在這地方
Now?
我無所謂 但他們就不知道了
I admire your boldness, but what will the team think?
等等 不是這意思
What? No, not...
好吧 我怕了你
Okay, you got me.
是說我們訓練的那一招 請
The training move, please.
上卡車
Get in the truck.
你們的義務已盡
Your service has come to an end.
再見
Bless you all.
小心點 哥們兒 那些可是我的朋友
Watch it, dude. Those are my friends.
別搞得在像在管束你舍友一樣 甲殼
At least act like you're trying to keep your parasite in line, Beetle.
膽子真小
That was unbearable.
你說呢
Get it?
無聊
Seriously?
你能別把自己暴露給敵人嗎
Could you not leave yourself open like that?
我擔心
I worry.
對不起寶貝
I'm sorry, babe.
我最近想了很多
I've been doing a lot of thinking lately.
關於什麼的
About what?
我覺得我們的關係應該進展到下一步
I think we should take the next step in our relationship.
下次再說
To be continued.
說茄子
Say cheese,
發送
and post.
晚上一起看電影怎麼樣
Hey, how about a movie tonight?
繼續走你的 馬蓋拉
Keep moving, Magilla.
基地是我們的了
The base is ours.
剛才我們被打斷前 你打算說什麼來著
So, what were you saying before we were interrupted?
我
I...
好吧 哪都一樣
Okay, good a place as any.
我在城裏有一所公寓
I got an apartment in the city.
也許我們能分享一下
I hoped, maybe, we could share, you know,
你知道 住一起
together.
哦 好吧
Oh, snap!
裏面竟然不是一顆石頭
No rock?
這可真夠差勁的
That's so lame.
在塔瑪拉 我們其實很隨便的
On Tamaran, everyone would gossip.
所以我們可以住在一起
So it's a good thing we live here.
我覺得他們不太傳統
What I'm getting is that they're too good to hang with us.
是嗎 你在嫉妒嗎
Yeah, that's the takeaway.
粉絲過百萬了
Hey, I'm over a million followers!
我贏了
Call me Jefe.
你得把注意力放在遊戲上
You need to get your head in the game, gar.
或者你的心思在另一種遊戲上
Or, maybe your head is in a different game.
我這麼棒 竟然沒人約我
Who wouldn't want to date me? I'm awesome.
可我不管做什麼 都沒用
But everything I do pisses her off.
想聽聽我的建議
Want my advice?
別再變成猩猩然後去偷吻了
Quit turning into a chimp and stealing monkey kisses.
可人們覺得那樣可愛啊
People think that's adorable.
不 沒人那麼想
Nope, no one thinks that.
好了
Time out.
我得去打通電話
Gotta make a call.
土石女
Terra.
陪我過幾招
Would you like to join me?
這東西能幫我沉下心來
The staff helps clear the mind.
不 謝謝
No thanks.
我只想離那綠豆子遠一點
I'm just trying to avoid green bean for a while.
我從來都不關心動物園發生了什麼
I never cared much for the zoo.
如果他騷擾你..
If he's bothering you...
他只是個混蛋
He's just a jerk.
關於她的流言是真的嗎
Is it true what they say about her,
她父親被她困在了她額間的寶石裏
that she has her father trapped in that Jewel on her head?
是的 他的名字叫鬼父
Yes, his name is Trigon.
他是一個惡魔
He's a demon.
他們之間有間隙
They have issues.
好吧 起碼她知道去哪能找到她的父親
Well, she knows where she can find him.
你該多和她談談
You should talk to her more.
你就會發現渡鴉非常
You'll find that Raven can be quite
有趣
interesting.
不 謝謝了 我有點怕她
No thanks. Too creepy for me.
米拉格羅 聽起來不錯
Sounds like a good time, Milagro.
你拿到我的禮物了嗎
Did you get my gift?
當然 永遠的十七歲的禮品卡 我的最愛
Sure did. Gift card to the seventeen forever. My favorite.
媽媽和爹地想跟你說話 愛你
Mom and dad wanna say hi. Love you.
瞧我的寶貝兒子
There's my baby boy!
你能吃飽飯嗎
Are you getting enough to eat?
是啊 你過得怎麼樣
Yeah, how's it goin'?
還是不太喜歡我 哼
Still doesn't like me, huh?
他在改變
It's getting better.
別提那東西了
Let's not talk about that thing.
轉眼兩年過去了
It's been two years.
我正在努力 爸爸
I'm working on it, dad.
但這很難 你知道
But it's hard, you know.
他有自己的想法
It's got a mind of its own.
還有自己的脾氣 奧多
- And a temper. - Aldo.
他和一群超級英雄在一起
For god's sake. He's with a bunch of super heroes.
超人或是誰能把那東西弄下來
You think superman or someone could take that thing off him.
你應該冷靜一點
You're supposed to calm down.
我們不能把每次通電話都這樣結束
We can't have every call end this way, Aldo.
海梅不想我們討論這個問題
Jaime won't wanna talk to us.
為什麼是蛋糕
Why is the cake
出去嗎 這不是時候
coming out? It's not time!
啊 你的姨媽 慷蘇拉 簡直神經了
Ah, your aunt, Consuela, esta loca.
去吧 媽媽 我們可以之後再聊
Go, mom, we can talk later.
我愛你 海梅
I love you, Jaime.
保重
Be good.
慷蘇拉 把蛋糕給我
Consuela, give me that cake!
我最好也走了
I better go too.
真抱歉 只是
I'm sorry. It's just...
我想我的兒子
I miss my son.
正在打開最近的 血兄弟 片段
Accessing most recent footage on brother blood.
一派胡言
Lies.
我的教堂是神聖的地方
My church is a holy place
我們唯一的使命是做正確的事
and we strive only to do good.
拜託  血兄弟
Come now, brother blood.
你的教堂難道不是另一個光榮化的邪教嗎
Isn't your church just a glorified cult?
不像你 布賴斯 我堅信著美國
Unlike you, Bryce, I believe in an America
所有信仰都應被給予應有的尊重
where all beliefs should be treated with respect.
可恥的事媒體認為並非如此
It's a shame the press doesn't.
恐怕這是我們能從血會得到的所有消息了
I'm afraid that's all we're going to get from brother blood.
我是彼得森 布賴斯
I'm Bryce Peterson.
晚安
-Have a good night.
祖父一定會為血兄弟
Grandfather would have been impressed with blood,
經營著像蜂巢一樣一個世界範圍的邪教而驕傲
running a worldwide cult as well as H.I.V.E.
他們本為一體
They're the same thing.
只是讓他們看起來是分開的而已
He just makes them look separate.
你從來都不脫掉那制服嗎
Do you ever get out of that uniform?
只有洗澡時候才脫
Only when I bathe.
也許是時候了
Might be time.
沒味道
I'm good.
我出去了
Goin' out.
我聽說你總是出去
I hear you're gone a lot.
你去哪
Where do you go?
你知道我是不需要大人管小孩
You realize I'm not a child who needs permission to go outside.
對吧
Correct?
達米安 我不是在審問
Damien, I wasn't interrogating.
只是感興趣而已
Just taking an interest.
我出去巡邏
I go out on patrol.
對了  恭喜你有了新歡 格雷森
By the way, I should offer congratulations on your cohabitation, Grayson.
星火證明她是一個夠格的領袖
Starfire has proven herself to be a decent leader.
我同意
I approve.
謝謝你
Thank you.
你在蜂巢文件裏找到什麼了嗎
Have you found anything in the H.I.V.E. Files?
沒什麼  但我仍在查
Nothing Earth-shaking, but I'm still checking.
聽起來你什麼都沒查到
Sounds like you got squat.
我至少還能享受下正常生活
I love endangering my life for nothing.
上次突襲拿到的新的文件
Which is why I've added the newest files to the ones
已經損毀的無法閱讀了
too damaged to read, from the previous raids.
希望電腦能為我們找到其中的關聯
I'm hoping the computer will find a connection we missed.
程序得花一到兩天處理這些信息
It may take the program a day or two.
至少還有希望
Not your worst idea.
幹嘛
What?
呃
Ugh!
嘿 你們誰見傑米了
Hey, anyone seen Jaime?
他就在那兒
Yeah, he's right there.
有點不對勁
Something is wrong.
是啊 他輸掉球賽了
Yeah, there is. He's about to be crushed at Foosball.
你想來瞧瞧嘛
You wanna come see?
起開
Buzz off.
也許你應該去
Maybe you should go.
也許你們兩個都去是個好主意
Might be good to have two of you down there.
如我所說 不服從的人
And I say to you. Those who deny the chosen,
在即將建立的樂園中沒有棲腳的地方
have no place in the Eden that shall be built.
罪人和褻瀆者 那些與我們價值觀念不同的人
Sinners and blasphemers who do not share our values
將被拋棄
need not apply,
兄弟姊妹們
brothers and sisters.
全能的 兄弟血會
Hail, brother blood!
萬歲 萬歲 萬歲
Hail, hail, hail.
全能的 血色兄弟
Hail, brother blood.
萬歲 萬歲 萬歲
Hail, hail, hail...
啊 你在這兒 邁赫姆
Ah, there you are, mayhem.
你為何
Punctual as always.
這麼冷靜的
How can you be so calm?
這是第三個被少年泰坦摧毀的基地
That was the third base the Titans have destroyed.
我的計劃歷經九百年的風雨
My plan is nine centuries in the making.
每個年代都有人反抗
In every age, there are always those who oppose me.
但如你所見
But as you can see,
我總是贏家
I am always victorious.
這是那個記者嗎
Is that the reporter?
是他
Yes.
我們的朋友再也不會問出那些粗魯的問題了
Our friend won't be asking impertinent questions anymore.
他的質疑遠不及少年泰坦帶來的威脅
His heresy does not compare to the titan's threat.
我們幾乎無法逃脫他們
We barely escaped them.
但你做到了
But you did,
因為他警告過你
because he warned you.
我們的守護天使
Our guardian angel.
別做無謂的擔心了
Oh, stop your fretting, mayhem.
他會保證泰坦不搗亂
He'll keep the Titans at bay.
我已預見
I've foreseen it.
再加上 我付那混蛋足夠的錢
Plus, I pay the bastard enough.
你能慢點嗎 傑米
Could you slow down, Jaime?
那你回塔上吧
Go back to the tower then.
沒人請你來
Nobody asked you to come.
噢 別這樣 我們可是挺你的
Oh, come on. We're here to support you.
我可不是
I'm not.
我的意思是 我尊重傑米的意見
What I mean is, I respect Jaime not wanting to talk.
事實上 有些人應該好好學學怎麼閉上他的嘴巴
In fact, more people should learn to shut their mouths.
好吧 那可真沒意思
Well, that's no fun.
呃 好吧 我閉嘴
Uh, okay, I give up.
瞧
The center.
我的父母在鄉下也做義工
My parents volunteer for the one in my town.
所以....
And...
也許我也該做義工
Maybe I should volunteer.
是的 沒錯兒
Yeah, right.
我們是泰坦
We're Titans.
我們不是給人舀湯的
We don't serve soup.
你不需要非得移動座山
You don't have to move a mountain
才算幫助別人 泰拉
to help people, Terra.
況且 我得想個辦法
Besides, I gotta find a way to make the bug
讓蟲子在人類附近覺得更加舒服
more comfortable around humans.
我能幫你什麼嗎
Can I help you?
是的 呃
Yes, um,
崔西
Traci.
我想知道如果我想做義務勞動應該找誰
I was wondering who I can speak to about volunteering?
找我就對了
That would be me.
這下好了
And there it is.
僅僅因為我們的超能力
Just because we have powers
並不意味著我們就不能 你知道
doesn't mean we can't, you know,
建立關係
have relationships.
你不覺得嗎
Don't you think?
嘿 享受生活沒錯兒 對嗎
Hey, there's nothing wrong with having a life, right?
殺了她
Kill her!
殺了這個惡魔
Kill the demon!
怎麼了
What's the matter?
沒什麼
Nothing.
真是差勁 我要離開
This is lame. I'm out.
在這千年裏  我在敵人的血中沐浴
For nearly a millennium, I have bathed in my enemy's blood,
這麼做
and for some mysterious reason,
可以使我永生
it has provided me immortality.
我總是好奇為什麼
I have often wondered why?
為什麼是我
Why me?
但現在我知道了
But now I know.
這是 天意讓我
It was meant to bring me to this age,
在此地 在此時
this place, this moment,
借助科技的力量
where technology can at last be made to serve my greatness.
運行
Proceed.
你做的非常好
You've done well.
開始準備 邁赫姆 時機已到
Advance the preparations, mayhem. The time has come
讓我們永生之榮耀
for us to move from immortality to glory.
多謝你的付出
Your service has come to an end.
祝福你 我的孩子
Bless you, my son.
作為宇宙公主
For a space Princess,
你的東西還真不少
you sure have a lot of stuff.
我還是小女孩的時候就有這個了
I've had this since I was a little girl.
這是我唯一有時間拿走的東西
It was the only thing I had time to take.
又來
Not again.
泰拉 你還好嗎
Terra, are you okay?
她就快要把整個樓都弄到了
She's going to bring the building down.
我能幫助她
I can help.
你在幹嗎
What are you doing?
滾開
Get off me!
你在發動你的能力  土石女
You were shaking everything, Terra.
我們來看你
We came to check on you.
你還好嗎
Are you all right?
只是個該死的噩夢罷了
It's a freaking nightmare.
你們快走吧 讓我一個人靜一靜
Just leave me alone.
我很好 所以 走吧
I'm okay, so, get going.
你們聽見我說的樂 走啊
You heard me. Get going.
還有你 綠豆芽
You too, greeny.
這種事發生得多嗎
Does that happen a lot?
足夠多
It happens enough.
你看到什麼了 什麼都沒看到
- What did you see? - Nothing.
而且就算我看到任何東西也跟你沒關係
And if I did see anything, it wouldn't be your business.
塔裏發生的一切都跟我有關係
Everything that goes on in the tower is my business.
不管是誰
Just like it should be for all of you.
據我所知 達米安 柯莉安才是頭 而不是你
The last I checked, Damien, Kori was in charge, not you.
很高興再次見到你 我的朋友
So good to see you again, my friends.
已經過去太長的時間
It's been too long.
太長了
Too long.
別把這搞得神經兮兮 布拉德
Don't make this weirder than it already is, blood.
你是說裝束
Are you referring to the setting?
我自己從中獲取力量
I myself take strength from it.
墓地不是一個該被畏懼的地方
The cemetery isn't a place to be feared.
而是重生的地方
It's a place of renewal.
對你我見面的地方我沒有任何意見
I have no problem meeting anywhere you want,
但我擔心我的僱主是個神經病
but I get concerned when my employer talks to himself.
我在跟死者說話
I talk to the dead,
無論屍體如何腐爛 總是有一線生氣存留
for no matter how rotted the corpse, there's always a tiny wisp of life left.
有時候足夠把它們帶回來
Sometimes enough life to bring them back.
你們都該明白
You of all people should know that.
你想要什麼 布拉德
What do you want, blood?
我想在一周內得到進展
I want to move everything up by a week.
我已經等待了足夠久的時間 喪鐘
I've waited long enough, Deathstroke.
這不是我們約好的
That wasn't the deal.
我會付你雙倍的酬金
I'll double your price.
這可以接受嗎
Is that acceptable?
就像之前 我要所有的泰坦
As before, I want all the Titans.
你能做到嗎
Can you do it?
時刻準備著
To be ready for anything,
你們必須為一切情況而訓練
you must train for everything.
這是歐喀拉的軍閥教我的
That was the most important lesson
最 刻骨銘心的教訓
instilled in me by the warlords of Okaara.
又是他們
Dude... Them again?
老兄
Dude...
這同樣應該在你們的心中銘記
And so it shall be instilled in you.
讓我們對練
Let's pair off.
那些不在戰鬥中的 就觀察學習
Those not fighting, watch and learn.
夜翼
Nightwing.
讓我們起舞 先生
Shall we dance, good sir?
當然 我的女士
But of course, my lady.
看來我們知道是孰強孰弱了
Guess we know who's taking out the garbage at the new place.
這對你沒一點好處
That was not a confidence booster.
你做的非常好
You did very well.
你這次堅持的時間遠遠要比以前久
You lasted far longer this time.
我當然指的是訓練
I meant in training, of course.
當我們... 他可是非常熟練
He's very proficient when we have...
柯莉
Kori!
藍甲蟲 渡鴉
Blue Beetle, Raven.
抱歉 渡鴉 蟲子不想輸
Sorry, Raven, the bug doesn't wanna lose.
難道你想
And you do?
真對不起 你還好嗎
Dios mio! I'm so sorry. Are you okay?
你在做什麼
What the hell are you doing?
阿 我沒事
Ah, I'm fine.
父親覺得我讓自己蒙羞
But dad feels I've disgraced myself.
所以就很好
So that's nice.
野獸小子 土石女 你們準備好了嗎
Beast Boy, Terra, you ready?
抱歉
Right. Sorry.
我會讓著土石女的
I'll take it easy on Terra.
我可很享受讓你閉嘴
I'm gonna enjoy shutting you up.
除非你能抓到我 老媽
Only if you catch me, mama.
親愛的 就讓我給你一個大擁抱
Mon Cherie, let Garfield give you a big hug.
嗯 好軟
Mmm, so soft.
親下你再放你走
I let you go for a little kiss.
殺了她
Kill her!
女巫 你罪有應得
Now, witch, you get what's coming to you!
你管誰叫女巫
Who you calling a witch?
土石女
Terra!
她打算殺了他
She's going to kill him!
啊
Argh!
土石女 控制你自己
Terra, control yourself!
什麼
What?
怎麼回事
What's going on?
抱歉 這不是我的錯
I'm sorry, it's not my fault.
讓我平靜下你的心 不
- Let me calm your mind. - No!
別碰我 沒關係的 土石女 我們理解
- Don't touch me. -It's okay Terra, we understand.
放鬆
Take a breath.
我們在這裏是為了你
We're here for you.
是啊 我知道你並不想傷害我 只是我做的太過了
Yeah. I know you didn't mean to hurt me. I took it too far.
你們這些人是怎麼回事兒
What's wrong with you people?
我知道你打算說什麼 土石女需要更多的訓練
I know what you're going to say. Terra needs more training.
不 是別的事兒
No, it's something else.
她知道一些
She knows.
自從我們談過之後 我已經感受到了關於土石女的一些東西
Since we talked, I have sensed something off about Terra.
格雷森 我們要多注意她
She needs to be watched, Grayson.
她需要理解而不是監視
She needs understanding not surveillance.
土石女 她雖然不是完人  但科裏認為她是值得的
Terra, has her rough edges. But Corey thinks she's worth it.
我同意他的
And I agree.
你的仁慈 遲早會出事
Making decisions with your heart will get people killed.
不能有人和我
It's not like I can't sense the vibrations of someone following me.
即使他們在屋頂上
Even if they are on a roof.
我知道你不喜歡這個
I know what it's like not to fit in with the group.
什麼錯
What's wrong?
猴子男孩 渡鴉
Aside from monkey boy making me melt down, or Raven staring all the time,
還有夜翼 像個老媽媽 海梅還有他的甲蟲
Nightwing, acting like a den mother, Jaime and his freako bug,
嗯 還有你 我的又一個暗戀者
miss smiles-a-lot, and you, my new stalker,
你沒什麼要說吧
huh, nothing I guess.
你需要我們的幫助
If you need to talk
就告訴我們
let us help you.
多麼貼心的男孩
Such an observant, considerate boy.
你不會是真心的吧
You would think he truly cares.
斯萊德 你還沒死啊
Slade? Look what hell just spit up.
退後
Stay back.
讓我猜猜 他們不要你嗎
Let me guess, they got you to a Lazarus pit, just in time.
先讓你過過嘴癮
Yes, I've been bathing in it quite a bit, lately.
待會就
You might say, it's addictive.
要你哭
Improves muscle tone too.
你的鋒芒沒了
Losing your edge.
你的朋友讓你變的軟弱
Your friends have made you soft.
就像我說的
Like I said, soft.
怎麼這麼久
Took you long enough.
你背叛了我們 為什麼
You betrayed us, why?
背叛
Betrayed?
我從來就不是你們這邊的
That assumes I was ever on your side in the first place.
給你 費爾南德斯先生
There you go, Mr. Fernandez.
- 很高興有你的幫忙  謝謝你 不
- Great to have your help. Thanks. - No.
應該是我說謝謝
Thank you.
這裏
I kinda needed this.
讓我想起了家
This just reminds me of home.
高溫 小心
- Ow! Huh, hot. - Careful.
你可不想被燒傷吧
You don't wanna get burned.
你有聽到什麼嗎
Do you hear that?
好像在那
- I heard it before. - Uh...
我希望他們命夠長
I hope there's not a short.
我想我知道它們在哪裏
I think I heard it move over there.
我知道我心跳的很厲害
I know my pulse is racing.
但我沒有危險 沒有
But I'm in no danger. None.
不需要防禦措施   我 怎麼解釋
Defensive measures are not needed. Oh, boy, how do I explain this?
稱為性吸引力
There's something humans call sexual attraction.
唉 命啊
Aye, my life.
嗯 海梅
Uh, Jaime?
你在做什麼
What are you doing?
我以為這會讓你更舒服
I thought I'd get more comfortable.
不要
Don't.
你不能這麼做
You can't run over here at the first sign of trouble.
我以為我失敗了
I was losing it. I had to see you.
幸運的是羅賓自投羅網
Luckily taking Robin out works.
只是一個人而已
Grabs a handful.
想個辦法把他也弄出來
Best to get him out of the way.
他總是很多疑
He was suspicious.
永遠是
Always is.
他很聰明
Didn't say he was stupid.
損壞了相機鏡頭
He damaged the camera lens.
格林妮做的
Greenie was asking for it.
需要很多時間才能打敗泰坦
It's taken a year to get the information I need to defeat theTitans.
別動
Could've ruined everything. Stay still.
- 殺了她  - 殺死女巫
- Kill her! - Kill the witch!
殺死女巫 她是個惡魔
Kill the witch! She's a demon!
殺了她
Kill her now!
離開或死亡
Leave or die. Your choice.
馬拉姆 泰拉
Terra Markov?
我聽說你是一個特別的女孩
I heard you're a special girl.
這是真的嗎
Is that true?
我的名字是斯萊德
My name is Slade.
看來我找到了
Looks like I got it.
不 你沒有
Not yet, you haven't.
但你可以
But you could.
- 我們討論過這個 - 我不是一個孩子
- We discussed this. - I'm not a kid.
- 你說我們會在一起- 還沒 到時候
- You said we'd be together. - Not yet.
任務要緊
The contract is everything.
我們需要先處理眼前的事
We need total concentration for it.
你知道還有很多工作要做
You know it's taken a lot of work to get here.
- 尤其是你  - 我不想回去
- Especially by you. - I don't wanna go back.
泰坦表現的好像他們在關心我
The Titans are always acting like they care so much.
這讓我不知所措
It messes with my head.
馬上就好 泰拉
Just a little longer, Terra.
有了血會的錢 我們將有自己的刺客聯盟
With the money from blood we'll form our own league of assassins.
你和我
You and I.
將浪跡天涯
Together in every way.
我還沒看到過這麼多武器
I didn't see you bringing quite so many weapons to our new place.
如果你不喜歡 不不不 我喜歡
- If you don't like them... - No, no. They're great.
有事嗎
Is something up?
在訓練場的事件之後
After the incident at the training field
我覺得你不需要我也可以統領他們
you met with members of the team without me.
是 這不一樣
Yeah, we talked. But it wasn't a meeting.
柯莉 你知道我永遠不會破壞你 對吧
Kori, you know I'd never undermine you, right?
他們需要你
They went to you.
你是...是一個偉大的領導者
You were... Are a great leader.
所以 他們盼著你回來了
So, they instinctively look to you, now that you're back.
畢竟 我不是你們這個世界的人
After all, I'm not even from your world.
不要這樣
Hey. Stop.
泰坦們選擇你來領導他們
You were chosen by the team to lead them.
而且我不能沒有你
And have I told you how glad I am that you've chosen to move in with me?
我至少還有你
At least I was your first choice for that.
沒錯 你至少可以住我這
Yeah. Well, gar's got his house and Jaime couldn't afford the rent.
你這個傢伙
You brat.
達米安 當然
Damian! Of course.
真會挑時間
Perfect timing.
- 什麼事 - 他在做某事
- Solo? - He's working on something.
待會再管
Have I mentioned he approves of us?
復議
So do I.
幹嘛
Yeah? Problem?
沒啥事
Not yet.
那就再見
Nice visit.
我知道我們之間有矛盾
I know I'm not easy to get close to.
我們要談談
We have that in common, I think.
而且我也有辦法緩解你的精神問題
But I could teach you some meditation techniques.
讓你更好的控制自己
It might help you stay in control.
那 那也許
Maybe. Maybe so.
還有 我們要舉行聚餐活動
The other reason I'm here is to tell you the team's assembling in the common room.
你先走 我待會就來
I need a minute. You go on ahead.
他們知道了
They know about Robin.
他們不知道
They don't.
掠奪者 沒問題嗎
Raven, being nice?
我怎麼不知道有聚餐這一回事
And there's nothing scheduled.
除非他們知道我和你在合作
They know I'm working with you.
如果他們知道 就不會讓她一個人過來
If they knew, she wouldn't have come alone.
除非他們想讓我放下戒備
Unless they wanted to get my guard down.
我不知道我能不能成功
I don't think I can take them all if they're ready.
冷靜  他們沒有懷疑你
Calm yourself. The fools trust you.
放輕鬆
Use that.
驚喜
Surprise!
該死
Shit.
你們嚇到我了
You guys scared me.
你們幹什麼
We can see that.
- 為了我嗎 - 是的
- Are those for me? - They sure are.
作為你的一週年泰坦紀念日
For your one year anniversary as a member of the Titans.
- 渡鴉想出來的主意  - 我...
- It was all Raven's idea. - I...
從沒有人為我這麼做過這樣的事情
No one has ever done anything like this for me.
謝謝
Thanks.
非常感謝
Thanks a lot.
抹乾眼淚 開始嗨皮吧
Dry those tears and let's get this party started, mama!
電腦處理完了
The computer's done.
- 血會的文件  - 讓我們看看
- The one with blood's files. - Let's take a look.
文件重構和集成完成
File reconstruction and integration complete.
這個科學家曾經為蜂巢工作
That scientist used to work for H.I.V.E.
沒有找到屍體
Body never recovered.
似乎他的個人實驗室仍在為
Seems his personal lab is still being paid for
血會的子公司服務
by one of blood's holding companies.
泰坦們應該來看下
The Titans should look into this.
看來你要錯過為
Beast Boy's sending you pictures of Terra』s party.
泰拉舉辦的聚會了
Shame you're missing it.
你就這麼點本事嗎
You should go. Playing with teenagers is about your speed.
小子 激將法對我無用
I'm not gonna let you bait me, kid.
哦 可惜
Oh, what the hell.
切
Big man.
你不讓我離開這裏
Why not get me out of here so I can defend myself properly?
- 是不是你在害怕 - 真的嗎
- Unless, you're afraid. - Really?
把你放了 然後再打一架
You're down to hoping I'm gonna act like the biggest stooge in a b-movie?
你不這麼想嗎
Your outfit said give it a shot.
你以為你是誰
Grandson of the demon's head, you are not.
你只是一個小屁孩
You're an entitled brat.
當我崛起時你還不知在哪
I Rose from nothing while you had everything handed to you.
你只是一個跳樑小丑
You cost me my rightful place.
和你背叛的家庭
And the family you betrayed.
他們選擇了你
They turned on me by choosing you.
達米安 刺客聯盟沒了
You took my old family, Damian.
不過我會再創造一個新的
So I'll take your new one.
我先離開會
I should reply.
我們走的瞧
I am well and will see you soon.
你更像另一個迪克
You're more of a dick.
臥底 別打擾我
Undercover. Don't bother me.
我不會花很多時間
Shame I don't have more time to break you down.
只要一個月 我就會讓你跪地求饒
Inside a month, I'd have you bringing me my pipe and calling me papa.
斯勒德 待會再說
Slade? Get your head out of your ass.
- 聽到嗎 - 如果我們找到科學家
- You seeing this? -And if we do find the scientist,
我們要活捉他
we want him alive at all cost.
五分鐘後行動
We leave in five minutes.
乖乖呆著
Be a good boy.
小心
Careful. Watch your spacing.
有有沒有主意
Any idea what that gizmo is?
沒有
Nothing good.
待會再吵
He's deleting. I vote we stop that.
讓我們兩個
That makes two of us.
好吧 三個
Okay, three.
遠離電腦 就完事大吉
Step away from the computer. You won't be hurt.
你先去 我隨後到
Go after him. I'll cover you.
我們應該留在聚會上
We should have stayed at the party.
沒什麼好抱怨
Quit complaining.
那我就奉陪到底
Oh, you wanna play?
差勁
That's it? Lame.
你想先問他什麼
What do you want to ask him first?
倒霉
Bad luck for him.
至少不是一無所獲
At least it wasn't one of us.
話沒錯
Yes, bad luck.
就是不能和他細談了
That we couldn't speak with him about these.
也許他是個粉絲
Maybe he was a fan?
他們竟然在研究我們
Is it really a surprise they would study us?
我們幾個月前就再與他們作戰
We've been defeating them for months.
這裏面竟然有你
And you were after them even before that.
他們調查的如此深入
But this stuff is so in-depth.
在調查我們的基因構造
Things on genetic makeup.
渡鴉與野獸男孩的
Theories on Raven's power.
力量來源
Beast Boy's too.
還有藍甲蟲
And Beetle's suit.
但為什麼
What's it for?
把羅賓召回來
We need to get Robin back here.
你知道他這人又多不守紀
You know how stubborn he can be.
他是我們的成員
He's a titan. He needs to be here.
都怪蜂巢打擾了我們的聚會
Nothing like laser-spewing H.I.V.E drones to take you out of a party mood.
我決定明天中飯在中心區吃
I'm beat and I'm making lunch at the center tomorrow.
真會潑冷水
In more exciting news,
我明天也受邀參加凱文·史密斯的播客聚會
I've been invited to be on Kevin Smith's podcast at Metrocon tomorrow.
等下 星火有事宣佈
Hold up, Starfire's got something to say.
由於今天晚上的發現
With what we discovered tonight,
我們將要提高警惕
we all need to be extra vigilant
不要疏忽大意
and not take any chances.
不是吧 那可是凱文·史密斯
Are you kidding me? It's Kevin Smith.
我沒有說禁止你們自由行動
I didn't say don't do what you have planned.
提高警惕 還有保持通訊暢通
But keep your eyes and comm lines open at all times.
我覺得兄弟血會要有所行動了
I have a feeling whatever blood is planning tonight is just a prelude.
抱歉你的聚會以這種方式結束
Sorry your party was interrupted.
這也沒辦法
That's the way it goes.
別又跟以前一樣
Don't let all that talk back there shake you up.
你知道我是你這邊的
You know I got your back.
其他的事
It's other stuff.
什麼
Like what?
我洗耳恭聽
I'm all ears.
你笑起來更好看
You've a pretty smile.
你知道我怎麼變成孤兒的嗎
Do you know how I became an orphan?
嗯 你的父母去世了
Uh, your parents died?
不是
No.
因為我的能力 他們嚇壞了
After I got powers, they freaked.
他們是我為異人
Thought I was possessed or something.
對不起
I'm sorry.
不要這樣
Don't be.
我不需要你的憐憫
I don't need your pity.
我只是想拉近我們的關係
It can be a bond, you know?
團隊裏的每個人都有一個不幸過去
Everyone on the team's had it rough.
是啊
Yeah.
一個公主 穿著閃閃發光的丁字褲從垃圾桶找食物
I can tell Princess sparkle thong knows all about eating from a dumpster.
柯莉被她妹妹奪了權
Kori is a refugee being stalked by her homicidal sister.
傑米有一個愛他的家庭
Jaime has a family that loves him.
由於那個甲蟲 他不能和他的家人生活在一起
And, because of the bug, odds are he's never seeing them face-to-face again.
每個英雄都有苦處
I think pain is what makes a hero.
金無足赤,人無完人
It's like a pressure that either forms a diamond or grinds you into dust.
開心果 你呢
But what about you, chuckles?
你又沒有什麼苦處
Aside from an unhealthy online presence, you're normal.
是啊 你是綠色的
Yeah, you're green.
你不會去改變它的
You wouldn't change it if you could.
你喜歡引人注目
You like the attention.
除此在外
Besides
你一切正常
it looks okay on you.
你沒殺我
You didn't kill me.
這一次
This time.
說明不了什麼 笨蛋
Don't get used to it, jerk.
高興 開心
Yes! Yeah!
我最牛 哈哈
Whoo-hew! Yeah, baby! Ha-ha!
我最強
Oh, yeah, baby!
我們走吧
Let's go!
開心
Nice play.
一切就緒
Almost bought it myself.
我們明天行動
We move tomorrow.
我有點累了 加油
I'm tired, gar.
是的 當然 好的
Yeah, sure, totally get it.
明天見還有後天
See you tomorrow. And the next day.
我會搞的
Yeah, I got them all in.
我知道我是蠢貨但我搞的定
Hey, I know I'm a noob but I got this.
再見
See you when you get here, .
這裏一定有很多人
The guest of honor with one million followers is...
是這沒錯吧
Uh, here?
有人嗎
Hello?
凱文或者其他人
Kevin? Other guy?
今天下午我們應該再好好把文件再複查一遍
I think we should look over the files again, this afternoon.
確保我們沒有遺落什麼
Make sure we didn't miss anything.
遵命
Sure thing.
一切安排聽從組織
And per your orders, I'll check on Jaime and gar.
你不必這樣做 但謝謝
You don't have to do that, but thanks.
還有
By the way...
我想我搞不定這個
The warlords of Okaara didn't teach me much about cooking.
看來要定外賣了
I think you should pick something up on the way back.
回見
See you soon, babe.
怎麼了
What's going on?
早應該開門了
Not sure. It should be open.
也許他忘了
We got a new guy.
傑米
Jaime?
泰坦藍甲蟲被抓走了
Titans, Blue Beetle has been taken.
在塔上集合
Gather at the tower.
這裏是柯莉和迪克 我們不在家
This is Kori and dick. We're not home now.
請留言
So leave a message.
星火接電話 我要去接野獸小子
Starfire, pick up if you're there. I'm going to get Beast Boy.
在塔樓匯合
Get to the tower now.
不是吧
Oh, come on, gar.
柯莉 你在嗎
Kori, you here?
柯莉
Kori.
喪鐘已敲響
Bad day, Nightwing?
末日來臨
It's about to get worse.
你對其他人做了什麼
What have you done with Kori and the others?
別擔心
Don't fret.
你馬上就回和他們見面了
I'm here to take you to them.
混蛋 休想
Bring it, asshole.
就這麼點
Akido needs work.
你就這麼點水平
Your spacing's for shit.
你太嫩了
You're overrated, kid.
該死
Damn it.
夠了
Enough.
該結束了
Screw this.
格雷森 你逃了又如何
You could have died by the Blade with honor, Grayson.
手下敗將
Loser.
任務完成了嗎
Is it done?
是 搞定了
Yeah, we're good.
他在騙你
He's lying to you.
所有的都是謊言
About everything.
他以此為生
He had you pegged from the start.
他為了達到目的
That's how he does it.
不惜手段
Mixing truth with lies.
你就繼續扯吧
You're so freaking annoying.
你知道什麼
You don't know anything about him.
他救了我的命
He saved me.
讓我猜猜 他讓你只
Let me guess, he kept you isolated.
依賴他
Dependent.
敵視所有人
Told you everyone was your enemy.
然後訓練你
Trained you, ruthlessly.
向你許下承諾
And promised you exactly what you wanted.
我知道他所有的套路
Believe me, I know.
我一直很討厭你
I've always hated you.
還有其他人
You and all the others.
泰坦對待你像家人
The Titans treated you like family.
而你卻背叛了我們
And you threw it all away.
閉嘴
Stop...
你先離開一會
Can't I leave you for two minutes?
我明白你為什麼要殺了他了
I can see why you want him dead.
怎麼了
What's wrong?
再過幾個小時 我們就離開這裏
In a few hours, we're gone.
任務完成了
It's as good as done.
很高興終於結束了
Just glad this is over.
你已經臥底了一年了
You've been in deep cover for a year.
對他們有感情是完全正常的
It's perfectly normal to have feelings for them.
以後就只有我們兩個了
But after this we can be together.
這不正是你所希望的嗎
Just like you wanted.
別讓他影響你
Concentrate on that.
電腦 跟蹤泰拉馬爾可夫的手機
Computer, track Terra Markov's phone.
已發現 主體正在移動
Discovered, subject is moving.
我想也是
I'll bet she is.
兄弟姐妹 我一再強調
Brothers and sisters, I have spoken many times
所謂的神
about false gods.
只不過是
These so-called heroes with no allegiance to our cause,
那些所謂的超級英雄
are nothing but secular idols and must be ended.
世間 只有我才是真正的神
This is the true house of faith and I am the one true god.
血兄弟萬歲 萬歲
Hail brother blood. Hail, hail!
現在聖光
Today, I am claiming their powers for us all.
已降臨到我們身上
For we are the seeds of the next generation.
我們蜂巢的身上
We are the hive of humanity.
再也不會有人來阻止
And nothing will stand in our way.
我降下聖光
Raise me this holy day.
我們將主宰世界
The day of blood.
兄弟血會萬歲 萬歲
Hail brother blood. Hail...
這個地方讓我毛骨悚然
Place gives me the creeps.
我聽到了
I hear you.
夥計們 渡鴉有點不對勁
Huh? Guys, Raven's not moving.
這裏有東西抑制了我的能力
Something's keeping me from using my powers to morph.
是的 機器就是這麼設計的
Yeah, the machine's doing that.
是我把你們放了進去
But, I'm the one who put you here.
喪鐘
Deathstroke.
你對羅賓做了什麼
What have you done to Robin?
他嘴巴太臭了
I beat the crap out of him for being mouthy.
你們也想試試嗎
Come on, you've all had the urge.
一旦我出來 我會揍你一頓
Once I get out, I'm gonna break you into little bits.
有理想
It's good to have goals, ese.
在你們死後我會好好的享受會的
Me, I'm having waffles, after you're dead.
順便 向你們介紹一下我的助手
By the way, can I introduce you to my assistant?
我想你們已經見過了
I think you've met.
隊友們 你們好啊
Hey, team, how's things?
泰拉 他對你做了什麼
Terra, what did he do to you?
沒什麼我已經問了很多次
Nothing. And I've asked a bunch of times.
泰拉是我安插在你們隊伍裏
Terra was a key part of my plan.
的間諜
A natural double agent.
這不可能是真的
That can't be true.
就像我說的
What can I tell you, Goldilocks.
有得必有失去
You win some, you lose some.
我們視你為隊友
We took you in.
誠心誠意幫助你
Helped you.
那就謝謝了
Yeah, well, thanks.
你們就等死吧
Now you're gonna die.
我還真有點不忍心啊
Geez, not a lot of gray area there, huh.
泰拉
Terra...
這地方讓我想起了我父母的教會
Place reminds me of my parents' church.
一堆瘋子
Bunch of crazies.
不知天高地厚的螻蟻
Insolent trash.
你管誰叫螻蟻
Who you calling trash?
冷靜
Keep it together.
對我們的客人禮貌點
Let's be civil to our guests.
契約還沒有完成
Our business is not yet complete.
沒有完成
Sure it is.
你想要泰坦 我把他們帶來
You wanted the Titans, and here they are.
不是全部
Not all of them.
少了夜翼
Not Nightwing.
這破壞了機器的平衡
It ruins the machine's symmetry.
死亡是不可避免的
We agreed some deaths might be unavoidable.
你要明白
Things happen.
我知道
I accept that.
而我也告訴過你
But I told you even in death there is life to be drawn.
屍體同樣有用
Where is the body? Unless you have a body, you're one short.
所以我們的合同還不完整
Therefore, our contract is not complete.
幸運的是 我們還有備胎
Happily there is still a path to the salvation of our deal.
不是嗎
Don't you agree?
很好
Excellent.
動手
Mayhem.
泰拉
Terra!
我要索要更多的報酬
I should have charged more.
有了她的力量 你猶如虎添翼
With her powers, you're getting an upgrade.
阿門
Amen.
現在 我們的契約已經完成
Now, our business is complete.
斯萊德 救我
Slade, help me.
對不起 孩子 生意就是生意
Sorry, kid. But a contract is a contract.
你會付出代價
You'll pay for this.
哦 甜心我也捨不得你
Oh, it's a shame you have to go, sweet cheeks.
我們相愛彼此
We would have been fantastic lovers.
我們對彼此一見鍾情
You know, since we're both newly single.
開始
Let it begin!
你認為你是神嗎 血兄弟
You think yourself a holy man, blood?
你只是個小人
You're filth.
緘口 罪人
Take heart, sinner.
你們將名垂青史
You are about to become part of the greater good.
要我們教你怎麼成名嗎
We're gonna show you the greater good.
就是踢你的屁股
By kicking your ass.
喪鐘 上帝不會饒恕你的
No god is going to save you, Deathstroke.
血兄弟
Word to the wise, blood,
你要對他們做什麼 快點做
whatever you're gonna do to them, do it quickly.
感覺不舒服
Not feeling so good.
他們罪有應得
I consider their pain a retribution for their sins against me.
對
Right.
你高興就好
Have a nice day.
先別急著走 等這個環節過了再說
Oh, don't leave now, brother. Everyone stays for this part.
什麼環節 血兄弟
What part is that, brother?
當他們的力量助我成神時
When their powers are transferred and I ascend to god state.
血弟兄們 聖光即將降臨
Hail me, brethren, for the moment of ascendency has arrived.
萬歲 血兄弟 萬歲 萬歲
Hail, brother blood. Hail, hail.
萬歲 萬歲萬歲
兄弟血會萬歲 萬歲
Hail, brother blood. Hail...
沒錯我的子民們  你們將見證我...
Yes, my children, this vessel shall now transform me...
成神之...
And you are witness.
血兄弟 萬歲 萬歲 萬歲
Hail, brother blood. Hail, hail.
我感到
I feel it.
爽
Yes!
我即將成神
My godhood is nearly complete.
讚美他
Praise him.
血兄弟萬歲
All hail brother blood.
萬歲 萬歲
Hail, hail.
爽....
Yes...
我知道你會來的
I knew you'd come.
嗨 老大爺 這是你的
Hey, papa, here's your pipe.
不要感謝我
Save some for me.
你們就不明白我是天命之子嗎
Don't you know, I am the chosen?
你們不知道 我是神...
Don't you know, I am divine...
我會殺了你
I'm gonna kill you.
你在利用我 不是嗎
I was being studied, like all the rest, wasn't I?
你從一開始就計劃這個權利
You planned this right from the start.
冷靜下來
Calm down.
我的愛 不是你想的這樣
This is all a big misunderstanding, love.
泰拉 不
Terra, no.
哦哦 該死
Oh, shit.
你這個異教徒
You heathen brats.
你毀了我的聖殿
You've destroyed my holy temple.
你奪走了我的神力
You've robbed me of my destiny.
我要殺了你
You will die.
你不會傷害...
You cannot harm...
不 滾開
No, you stay away from me.
你們這些惡魔
You demon filth.
他們不是惡魔
They're not demons.
我才是
Let me show you one.
什麼鬼
What the hell?
我準備了這麼久
I planned so long.
我是神 你們不明白嗎
I was destined, can't you see?
我懇求你
Please, I beseech you.
以血兄弟的名義
I am blood.
我...
I...
我是...
I am...
原諒我
Saved.
我不會讓他們抓住你的 我的愛
I won't let them cage you, my love.
快走
Come on.
孩子 再見
So long, kid.
泰拉..
Terra...
對不起
I'm sorry.
不 泰拉...
No, Terra...
- 不要... - 我們必須離開這裏
- No... -We have to go. The place is gonna collapse.
泰拉
Terra!
可以問你個問題嗎 你怎麼會成為一個泰坦呢
So, let me ask you this, man, how do you become a titan exactly?
我的意思是 有沒有試鏡什麼的
I mean, is there an audition? Do you look at videos?
我能不能成為一個泰坦
'Cause I've been working out, you know, I want in.
凱文 對我泰坦們泰坦來說
Well, Kev, I guess the most important thing to being a titan,
家庭最重要
is to have a strong sense of family.
有時我們也會因為性格不合
Some of us don't have our own, so, we support the ones that do.
而傷害彼此
Of course, an outgoing personality does hurt but, you know,
但你有超能力誒
you gotta have a power.
是挺帥的
Something cool.
帥 夥計你可以變身為動物 這也太酷炫了
Something cool? Listen, you turn into animals, man, that's beyond cool.
謝謝
Thanks.
這個能力不是來耍酷的
But, it's not just about the cool super powers,
穿上制服我們不能為所欲為
snazzy uniforms and daring adventures.
它使我們變得
It's about us helping each other grow.
更好
Be better people.
我知道你不想談論隊伍裏的人 但我還是忍不住
Listen, I know you're not supposed to talk about this, but I just gotta ask.
想問問那個女孩
There's a new girl, right?
她對我們來說意義非凡
All I can say is that she's a wonderful addition to the team.
繼續說 星火會殺了我的
- Come on, gar... - Starfire would kill me.
這事就你知我知
There's no way Starfire is listening to this, man, she's brushing her hair.
不要 沒門
Forget it. My lips are sealed.
他變成了只海豹
Whoa, man, he just turned into a seal, folks, I swear.
但是 加爾 她代替了土石女的位置嗎
But really, gar, is she gonna, like, replace Terra?
泰拉
Terra?
是的 你應該知道很多關於她的故事
Yeah, you know, there are lots of stories about her.
我知道
I know.
哦 太好了
Ooh, too soon?
是啊
Yeah.
我不是這個意思 如果你不想...
I mean, that's cool honestly, if you don't wanna...
但是 我想說..
But, I'd like to say something...
很多人幻想過一個完美的人生
There are a lot of people who've been handed a rough life.
他們沒有什麼需求 但...
They never asked for it, but...
他們盡其所能
They do what they can.
他們害怕被傷害
Many of them can't rise above the hurt.
但這太難了
It's just too hard.
但是最後 一切轟然倒塌時
But in the end, when the chips were down,
她找到了自我
and she finally showed her true self,
泰拉馬科夫是我見過的
Terra Markov was like a diamond.
後續彩蛋 勿走開
最偉大的人
Most beautiful thing that I'd ever seen.
就如我所說
I talk to the dead.
死亡不是終結
For no matter how rotted the corpse,
一切才剛剛開始
there's always a tiny wisp of life left.